[Music]
[音乐]
all right let's get it started
好吧，让我们开始吧
how's it going enjoying Barcelona good
巴塞罗那过得怎么样
right
对
how about you I'm enjoying myself great
你呢，我很开心
so how many of you actually have seen
所以你们当中有多少人真正见过
those cars lined next to the venue all
那些车子都排在会场旁边
of you yes
是你的
how many of you have a car so with we as
你们有多少人有车
people tower we have a quite a lot of
人塔我们有很多
experience when it comes to connected
连接方面的经验
cars technology which is on a on the
汽车技术在
edge right now and we'd like to share
马上就可以分享了
about that right absolutely so hence
关于这项权利绝对如此
this topic connect your car with spring
这个话题将您的汽车与 Spring 联系起来
toast since we have only like 50 minutes
敬酒，因为我们只有50分钟
yes we're going to spend like two of
是的，我们要花两个
them on introducing ourselves my name is
他们介绍自己的名字是
echo pin moon I work with spring
回声别针我和 Spring 一起工作
developer advocate and these are my main
开发者拥护者，这些是我的主要
areas of interest the when driven design
驱动设计时感兴趣的领域
test driven development architecture I
测试驱动的开发架构I
have a blog and Twitter account which is
有一个博客和Twitter帐户
probably the best way to reach me and
可能是联系我的最佳方式
also have a pet project which is TDD by
也有一个宠物项目，由
example if you are interested in that
例如，如果您对此感兴趣
please feel free to being a being a
请随时成为一个存在
tease happened that's it about me so my
挑逗发生的是关于我的，所以我的
name is Finn Mertens ashtag yeah most
最叫Finn Mertens ashtag是
likely
可能的
no idea that I should be here to talk
不知道我应该在这里聊天
because I'm not even there at the label
因为我甚至不在那儿
guys presentation so maybe I should just
大家介绍，也许我应该
go yeah get off my stage so I work in in
是的，离开我的舞台，所以我在
the spring cloud team as a developer and
Spring Cloud团队作为开发人员，
I'm leading the projects called spring
我正在领导 Spring 项目
cloud solution Sprint Cup contract thank
云解决方案冲刺杯合同感谢
you for clicking the button very good
你对于点击按钮很好
and also the areas of expertise are C
而且专业领域是C
ICD topics and my twitter handle is @nci
ICD主题，我的Twitter句柄为@nci
stock which I know this is impossible
我知道这是不可能的股票
for you to type so just go to my book
给你打，所以去我的书
too much coding come and you can find my
太多的编码来了，你可以找到我的
Twitter handle over there so we've got
Twitter在那里处理，所以我们有
coop we have given a presentation
小屋，我们给了介绍
testing your messaging application
测试您的消息传递应用程序
who has seen it I have nobody that was
谁看过我没有人
exactly what we expected so in that
正是我们期望的那样
presentation we had a little roleplay
演示中我们有一点角色扮演
that I was an ivory tower architect and
我是象牙塔建筑师，
I was in a company that had a very small
我在一家很小的公司里
budget to spend this is why we hired
花费预算，这就是我们聘用的原因
Jakob as a consultant and we are dealing
雅各布（Jakob）作为顾问，我们正在处理
with messaging and
与消息传递和
it resulted in me being fired in jail
导致我被判入狱
but now I found another job it wasn't my
但现在我找到了另一份工作，这不是我的
fault right of course I mean all the
当然是我的错
code you wrote compiled but didn't work
您编写的代码已编译但无法正常工作
but yeah so now I'm in a new company
但是，是的，所以现在我在一家新公司里
they don't know about my lack of
他们不知道我缺乏
knowledge of anything and the budget is
知道什么，预算是
even lower so again yaku is the only
甚至更低，所以雅库再次是唯一的
person that's why I'm here hire so yeah
这就是为什么我在这里雇用人的原因
cool thank you for being in this company
非常感谢您加入这家公司
as a consultant I spent like five
作为顾问，我花了大约五个
minutes on the reading what we do
分钟阅读我们的工作
exactly in this company maybe I'll share
正是在这家公司，也许我会分享
it with you all right
没事吧
when did you join this company and what
你什么时候加入这家公司的？
do you do ten minutes ago my first
十分钟前，我第一次吗
danger so what do I do here nothing
危险，所以我在这里做什么
special really which is no more thing
真的真的不再是什么了
and what does the company do so the
公司做了什么？
company deals with cars all right so we
公司处理好汽车，所以我们
write software that you know sends out
编写您知道发送的软件
messages some metrics from the car to
向汽车发送一些指标到
our apps and it does some analysis and
我们的应用程序，它会进行一些分析，
and then the other group so I read the
然后另一组，所以我读了
internal wiki and we have something like
内部维基，我们有类似
MQTT
MQTT
yeah from what I've heard MQTT is the
是的，据我所知，MQTT是
machine-to-machine protocol right um I
机器对机器协议权利
see that you're an amateur
看到你是一个业余爱好者
it's an m2m protocol this is how we
这是一个m2m协议，这就是我们
Enterprise architects College m2m all
企业建筑师学院m2m全部
right so it's m2m protocol aka a IOT so
对，所以它是M2M协议，又称IOT，所以
now you can be an Enterprise Architect
现在您可以成为企业架构师
as well it's a lightweight protonation
以及轻质的质子化
machines right yeah it's a lightly
机器对，是的，这很轻松
protocol that allows us to do pops up
允许我们弹出的协议
and since you know we're dealing with
既然您知道我们正在与
cars the code footprint has to be low in
汽车的代码占用空间必须低
order to make sense to use it and
为了使使用有意义
especially thing related to bandwidth is
特别是与带宽有关的是
important because if you know you're
重要，因为如果您知道自己
driving a car the networking changed the
驾驶汽车，网络改变了
Fuji for example so in order to
以富士为例
communicate we need to have you know low
沟通，我们需要让您知道低
bandwidth usage and also low power usage
带宽使用率以及低功耗
right so these are the important things
对，所以这些都是重要的事情
related to MQTT I haven't had more time
与MQTT相关，我没有更多时间
to actually read anything more about
实际阅读更多有关
this all right so quick question what
这可以这么快问什么
technologies do you use Oh so on the
您使用的技术是喔
back inside we have spring boot
回到里面，我们有 spring boot
applications and you know what I I'm an
应用程序，你知道我是什么
Enterprise Architect so whatever is
企业架构师，所以无论是
related to enterprise is my thing
与企业有关是我的事
I know enterprise integration patterns
我知道企业整合模式
for instance yeah this is
例如，是的，这是
in my life actually only the
在我生命中实际上只有
introduction anyways what I would like
反正我想要什么
to achieve is implement maybe one of the
实现是实施也许
patterns in order to you know Paul
为了你知道保罗的模式
information from some sort of an mqtt
来自某种mqtt的信息
broker or something so we need an mqtt
经纪人之类的东西，所以我们需要一个mqtt
broker running on this machine right now
立即在此计算机上运行的代理
I remember that the last time we met you
我记得上次我们见到你
had a rabbit and cube broker running on
有一个兔子和立方体经纪人正在运行
your machine
你的机器
oh yeah it's still running by the way
哦，对了，它仍然在运行
all the time right yeah okay so I'm to
一直都对，是的，所以我要
make it so you want mqtt on top of
做到这一点，所以你想要mqtt在
RabbitMQ right I don't know what I want
RabbitMQ对，我不知道我想要什么
I want to reuse what you have running
我想重用您正在运行的内容
there it's possible I'm happy to report
有可能我很乐意举报
that MQTT support it's supported by
MQTT支持
RabbitMQ house via plugin now so you can
RabbitMQ现在可以通过插件添加房屋，因此您可以
extend let's say rabbit by usage of
扩展，让我们说兔子的用法
plugins great that's correct so have it
正确的插件太棒了，拥有它
running and so we can leverage rabbit
运行，所以我们可以利用兔子
now how can we implement an enterprise
现在我们如何实施一个企业
integration pattern with rigor and weave
严谨和编织的整合模式
spring so we use spring boot right yes
Spring ，所以我们用 spring boot 吧
right now I'm happy to report that in
现在我很高兴在此报告
spring ecosystem we have this product
Spring 生态系统，我们有这个产品
which is called spring integration
称为Spring 整合
doesn't ring a bell
不打铃
I guess it's used for integration it's
我想它是用于整合的
used for integration I would say that it
用于整合我会说
implements it gives you a sprint
实现它给你冲刺
programming model to implement well now
编程模型，现在可以很好地实现
enterprise integration patterns right
企业整合模式正确
via declarative adapters so we can adapt
通过声明性适配器，以便我们可以适应
the challenge from instance from MQTT
MQTT实例带来的挑战
broker that's what we can do with spring
经纪人，这是我们 Spring 可以做的
integration spring board all right of
集成Spring 板
course we can try so this is a simple
当然我们可以尝试，所以这很简单
spring with application right there is
带有应用程序的Spring
spring integration on the class path
Spring 课程整合
okay so what's the first thing we need
好吧，我们首先需要什么
to do what do you think annotate
做你认为注释的事情
something yes of course let's start with
是的，当然，让我们开始
an annotation let's define a Bing
注释让我们定义一个Bing
which is responsible for actually giving
负责实际给予
me the connection factory to the actual
我连接工厂到实际
broker so we'll use amputee Parker
经纪人，所以我们将使用截肢者帕克
client factory which is basically first
客户工厂基本上是第一
party implementation of MQTT client so
MQTT客户端的第三方实现，因此
with the able to connect to the book yes
能够连接到书是
as you can see you have to pass
如您所见，您必须通过
something like you have to pass the
像你必须通过
overall to the actual server which is
整体到实际的服务器是
running on my local host port 180
在我的本地主机端口180上运行
t 183 then you have to pass some
t 183那么你必须通过一些
username which is predefined the
用户名，它是预定义的
password etc etc so that's the
密码等，这就是
connection factor right the client
客户的连接因素
factory to the actual broker what does
工厂给实际经纪人做什么
any ideas okay so we managed to connect
任何想法都可以，所以我们设法建立了联系
now we have to define something to
现在我们必须定义一些东西
actually start getting the messages so
实际上开始收到消息，所以
we have to we have to define the clarity
我们必须定义清晰度
adapter to the actual channel so MQTT
适配器到实际通道，因此MQTT
works as a pops up there are some topics
弹出窗口有一些主题
so we have to adapt the topic to
所以我们必须使主题适应
actually get some message produced to
实际上得到一些消息
your application right ok let's do it
好的您的应用程序，让我们开始吧
like this and yes so we can use MQTT
这样，是的，所以我们可以使用MQTT
path for messaging and adapter channel
消息传递和适配器通道的路径
and you have to pass the consumption
而你必须通过消费
idea let's say it's a US consumer D why
这个想法可以说是美国消费者D为什么
not what else need to pass the actual
没有什么需要通过实际
client factory which has defined
已定义的客户工厂
previously right like this and what else
以前是这样的，还有什么
we need to pass the actual topic what's
我们需要传递实际主题是什么
the name of the topic maybe something
主题名称可能
with my car cars or / cows / Marcin
与我的汽车或/牛/马辛
right ok mixes yeah what else wait to
好的，好吧，是的，还等什么
actually define the de flow from this
实际定义由此产生的流量
message channel and somehow handle it we
消息通道并以某种方式处理它
just create a beam that describes an
只需创建一个描述
option to fetch some data but now we
选择获取一些数据，但是现在我们
have to describe how it happens really
必须描述它是如何发生的
right exactly ok so we have to create
好的，所以我们必须创建
the inbound MQTT integration flow ok
入站MQTT集成流程确定
right that will be adapted via these MPs
通过这些国会议员改编的权利
message producer support doesn't make
消息生产者支持不起作用
sense so far sure alright so let's do
到目前为止，感觉还可以，所以让我们开始吧
that it's gonna be I guess MPT inbound
我猜是MPT入站了
right and we have to retune there's a
对，我们必须重新调谐
fluent API integration flows dot from
流利的API集成流程
MPs we need to handle somehow or maybe
我们需要以某种方式处理国会议员
do you want to transform it maybe let's
你想改变它也许让我们
give the payload so we got glass bailout
提供有效载荷，以便我们进行玻璃救助
right and how do you want to handle that
正确，您想如何处理
now let's use the logging framework we
现在让我们使用日志记录框架
have what's your logging frame or
有什么日志框架或
system.out.println all right
system.out.println好的
get right okay I think that's enough we
没事吧，好吧，我认为我们就足够了
have the integration flow we have the
有整合流程，我们有
message producer support we have the
消息生产者支持，我们有
actual connection factory to the broker
与经纪人的实际联系工厂
the broker is running let's start this
经纪人正在运行，让我们开始吧
application now so we have a we have an
现在申请，所以我们有一个
app that will listen to the messages
会听消息的应用程序
coming from the broker
来自经纪人
how will we simulate that the car sends
我们将如何模拟汽车发出的声音
the message so we can do it in various
信息，所以我们可以做各种
ways for instance by our CLI and there
通过我们的CLI等方式
is a tool called mosquito pop okay to
是一个叫做mosquito pop的工具，可以
actually talk to MQTT broker and listen
实际与MQTT经纪人交谈并听
to as well okay let's reuse this and so
好的，让我们重用它，如此
we're gonna pass let's clear it mosquito
我们要过去了，让我们清除蚊子
publish the name of the broker of the
公布经纪人的名称
lock the hosts of the brokers by default
默认情况下锁定代理的主机
localhost I don't need to reconfigure
本地主机，我不需要重新配置
that same up same applies to the port
同样适用于端口
what we need to pass the username which
我们需要传递的用户名是什么
was I guess user write the password and
我猜用户写密码了吗
the actual message which is what do you
实际的信息是什么
want to send hello hello why not and the
要发送问候你好为什么不和
topic which is in this case marching or
在这种情况下进行中的主题或
cars slash marching something like that
汽车大幅度前进，像那样
yeah it's correct I guess so
是的，我猜是对的
we'll see so if I type this what's it a
我们会看到的，所以如果我输入这是什么
couple of messages me why not it's for
几封邮件告诉我为什么不这样做
free it's for free as you can see you
免费，如您所见，它是免费的
got the message do you want to try a
得到消息，你想尝试一个
different topic maybe yes let's send it
不同的主题也许是的，让我们发送它
from my car why not you can't see
从我的车上为什么看不到
anything else
还要别的吗
hope you can see how it works awesome so
希望您能看到它的工作原理如此出色
we managed to implement an enterprise
我们设法建立了一家企业
integration pattern to actually get a
集成模式以实际获得
message and print it out which is great
消息并打印出来，这很棒
we've spring integration but you know in
我们已经进行了 Spring Integration ，但您知道
the in the last job you were paid by the
在上一份工作中，您的工资是
lines of code you have written you were
您编写的代码行是
right the thing is in this job it's not
正确的是这项工作不是
the case right so you wrote let's see
这个案例是正确的，所以你写了，让我们看看
free beans it's a couple of lines now we
免费 bean 现在有几行
get a bonus if we get to production
如果我们投入生产，将获得奖金
faster that's what the owners told me
业主告诉我的就是更快
now can we use some sort of a spring
现在我们可以使用某种Spring
integrations devious thing
整合de回事
frameworks so you want something which
框架，所以您想要一些
doesn't require you to write it
不需要你写
beans and actually stream information
bean 和实际流信息
from Robert yeah have you heard about
罗伯特·耶（Robert）是的，你听说过
spring cloud stream maybe I think there
Spring 的云流也许我认为在那里
was a presentation here about it were
这里是一个介绍
you here no III couldn't I was reading
你在这里，没有我不能读
the readme on the wiki about mqtt okay
Wiki上有关mqtt的自述文件还可以
so I'll try to briefly describes what
所以我将尝试简要描述一下
spring cloud stream is okay so in a
Spring 的云流还可以，所以在
nutshell it works like this you have an
简而言之，它像这样工作
application core which is middleware
应用程序核心是中间件
agnostic so in the application core you
不可知，因此在应用程序核心中
talk about your business logic and then
谈论您的业务逻辑，然后
at some point you are going to stream
在某个时候，您将要流式传输
information from input channel or just
来自输入通道的信息还是
send something to the output channel and
发送一些东西到输出通道
that's it when it comes to the
就是这样
application core as you can see it's
如您所见，应用程序核心
middleware agnostic so if I'm to explain
中间件不可知，所以如果我要解释
this to another Enterprise Architect I'd
我要交给另一个企业架构师
say that there is some code written and
说有一些编写的代码，
if I want to change one broker to
如果我想换一位经纪人
another I change a dependency pretty
另一个我改变了一个依赖
much
许多
yeah figuration yell code change yes
是的比喻大喊大叫代码更改是
sounds good
听起来不错
because of the binder interface because
由于绑定界面，因为
if you use springboard via auto
如果通过自动使用跳板
configurations going to see that you
配置将看到你
actually want to connect to rabbit or to
其实想连接到兔子或
Kafka okay depending on what's on your
卡夫卡好吧，这取决于您的情况
passport
护照
okay you want to see a sample let's do
好吧，你想看一个样本，让我们做
it we're going to connect to rabbit
它要连接到兔子
right yes so let's try it so there is a
是的，让我们尝试一下，有一个
second sample which is called spin cough
第二个样本，称为旋转咳嗽
stream application is the fourth big
流应用是第四大
enough great
足够好
so we want to see the palm maybe first
所以我们想先看看手掌
time is doing oh it haven't even
时间在做哦，甚至还没有
highlighted already always oh it's not
突出显示已经总是哦，不是
like where you go to the companies and
就像你去公司的地方
you have samples already prepared of
您已经准备好了样品
what your problems are not unique I
你的问题不是唯一的我
would say like
会说
let's dip it like this okay so you have
让我们这样蘸一下就可以了
the binder to rabbit okay we have the
兔子的粘合剂好吧，我们有
back you have the dependents it's a
回来你有家属
sprinkle stream so the only logical
洒流，所以唯一合乎逻辑的
conclusion from this that you can draw
由此可以得出的结论
is that you actually want to parent the
是您实际上想为父母
application color to rabbitmq that makes
应用到rabbitmq的颜色
sense that makes sense is it magic
有道理的感觉是魔法
I'd say it's engineering man okay so
我会说是工程人员，所以
thanks to this kind of engineering you
由于这种工程，你
can actually type things like that so we
实际上可以输入类似的内容，所以我们
need to define the number of channels we
需要定义我们的渠道数量
are going to talk to in this case is
在这种情况下要谈论的是
going to be how many channels so we have
将会有多少个频道，所以我们有
an application that listens to a channel
监听频道的应用程序
input or output there is an input
输入或输出有输入
channel all right so we have to enable
正确的频道，所以我们必须启用
bind to the definition of channels so
绑定到渠道的定义，所以
this situation in which you actually
这种情况，你实际上
talk to one input channel or one output
与一个输入通道或一个输出通话
Channel
渠道
it's kind of common so they are
这很常见，所以它们是
predefined interfaces one of them is
预定义的接口之一是
called sync okay all right and if you do
叫同步好吧，如果你这样做
like that you can take a look inside of
这样你就可以看里面
the same class and it actually has one
同一个班级，实际上有一个
input channel called input okay right
输入通道称为输入正常
and what do you want to do if there is
如果有的话你想做什么
something in common from this channel
这个频道的共同点
I'll get out of course it's gonna I'm
我会走开的，我会
gonna name it handle string right
要命名它正确处理字符串
message with system dot out all right
系统提示信息正确
why not yeah because you have to another
为什么不呢，因为你必须另一个
I don't know so we have to actually
我不知道，所以我们必须
teach your Springwood application and
教您的Springwood应用程序，并
sprinkle stream that this is the handler
洒流这是处理程序
you want to invoke each time there is
你想每次都调用
some incoming message okay make sense
一些传入的消息还可以
yes how to do that is as follows
是的，该如何做如下
let's trim the sinner to sink not sink
让我们修剪罪人沉沦而不沉沦
got input because this is the name of
得到了输入，因为这是
the yeah of the channel okay there is
是的，通道还可以
something more I want to I want you to
我想要的更多我想要你的
see okay so there is some small
好的，所以那里有些小
configuration in Yambol or properties do
Yambol中的配置或属性
you want to see that oh I love llamo do
你想看到哦，我爱llamo
it so as you can see we use a lot of
如您所见，我们使用了很多
companies a lot of em so you're familiar
公司很多，所以您很熟悉
with via moon so there's a destination
通过月亮，所以有目的地
to which you bind the actual input
您绑定实际输入的位置
channel write the summation is I'm p mq
通道写总和是我p mq
p dot topic
p点主题
I'm Q I'm sorry that topic which is the
我很抱歉，这个话题是
default topic used by Robin Q when it's
Robin Q使用的默认主题
the case with MQTT okay right working
MQTT的情况可以正常工作
right okay exactly and you have to pass
好的，好的，您必须通过
the actual pine including key to be
包括钥匙在内的实际松木
interested only in the information
只对信息感兴趣
coming from your specific topic which
来自您的特定主题
was first something margin yeah so to do
首先是保证金，所以要做
that meet the past binding routing key
符合过去的绑定路由密钥
if there is some type of please tell me
如果有某种请告诉我
okay and the topic was cars marching
好，主题是汽车行军
right why the dots because rabbiting
正确，为什么点因为兔子
field works like this with amputee t
野外截肢者这样的作品
that it translates slashes okay that's
它翻译斜线好吧，那是
it
它
so the binding routing key to the
所以绑定路由键
consumer it's gonna be slash cars
消费者将是削减汽车
marching this is the topic you are going
行军这是你要去的话题
to listen from right yes so let's start
从正确的地方听是的，所以让我们开始吧
this application if we start this
如果我们启动这个应用程序
application and I do mosquito publish we
应用程序，我做蚊子发布我们
should see something logged out
应该看到登出的东西
- yes these are the people's messages
-是的，这是人们的信息
okay they are waiting there so if I just
好吧，他们正在那里等，如果我只是
repeat this exercise let's pass
重复此练习，让我们通过
something different maybe hello hello
有些不同，也许你好
why not
为什么不
that's extremely intelligent yeah yeah
这是非常聪明的，是的
couple of them as you can see there
您可以在其中看到其中的几个
arrived so it works great awesome
到了，所以很棒
without any additional beans right so
没有任何额外的 bean 吧
thanks to sprinkle stream you don't have
多亏了你没有流
to pass like free beans which was the
像免费 bean 一样通过
case with spring integration actually
实际上是 Spring Integration 的案例
sprinkle stream uses spring integration
洒水使用Spring 整合
underneath oh I see okay this is this is
哦，我知道了，这是这个
great I really like it a lot but I would
太好了，我真的很喜欢，但是我会
like you to see our architecture in a
就像你看到我们的建筑
different way because we have those
不同的方式，因为我们有那些
clubs right and those cars and make
俱乐部权利和那些汽车，使
different types of metrics you know some
您知道一些不同类型的指标
of them are periodic like temperature
他们是周期性的像温度
speed like every 5 seconds or something
像每隔5秒之类的速度
like this every now and then right and
像这样不时地
you know if we have an information about
你知道我们是否有关于
current temperature if we lose it we get
当前温度，如果我们失去它，我们得到
it in 10 seconds that's not a problem so
在10秒内就没问题了
big deal make sense so this is this
大有道理，所以这是这个
periodic type of metrics and we have
定期类型的指标，我们有
another type of metrics which are what's
另一类指标是什么
the events say the car is braking the
事件说汽车在刹车
car and stop the car has stopped right
停下来，汽车已经停止了
and those are extremely extremely
那些非常极端
important so it'll be two questions the
重要的是，这将是两个问题
survey the first one can we leverage a
调查第一个，我们可以利用
protocol Navy to make some messages more
协议海军使一些消息更多
important than others yes you can do
比别人重要是可以的
that it's built into
它内置
mqtt protocol itself so we can actually
mqtt协议本身，所以我们实际上可以
provide different QoS levels okay I
提供不同的QoS级别
guess there are three levels level zero
猜猜共有三个等级零等级
is like fire-and-forget level one is
就像一劳永逸的一级
that you are going to acknowledge so
你会承认的
they sent you a message okay level two
他们给您发了一条消息，第二级
is as far as I remember that I'm going
据我记得我要走
to acknowledge that you acknowledge so
承认你承认
it's like a 4 Way handshake
就像四向握手
does it make sense yeah ok so that's one
是这样吗，那是一个
thing No
东西没有
so we've been integration there's just a
所以我们一直在整合，
setter for a specific topic like state Q
对特定主题（例如状态Q）的设置
s no I like setter so that's good so
不，我喜欢二传手，所以很好
another thing since these are different
另一件事，因为这些不同
types of metrics so maybe we could have
指标类型，也许我们可以
multiple channels maybe some you know a
多个渠道，也许您知道一些
little different top these different
有点不同，这些不同
channels to actually maybe scale out
实际可能扩大规模的渠道
some
一些
occasions that are going to you know
你想知道的场合
poll for certain messages or maybe
轮询某些消息，或者也许
inside a single application or I'd have
在单个应用程序中，否则我将拥有
different channels so maybe sprinkle
不同的渠道，所以可能撒
stream can support multiple channels
流可以支持多个频道
you're saying that you want to treat
你是说你想请客
them different yeah like different
他们不同，像不同
scaling reasons it's edgy because
缩放的原因，这是前卫的，因为
otherwise we'd have a single method and
否则我们只有一个方法
some sort of an if like if it's a
某种如果，如果它是一个
periodic one do this if it's a non
定期的，如果不是
periodic one do that so maybe we can
定期这样做，所以也许我们可以
handle it in a different way
用不同的方式处理
yes you can do that actually you are not
是的，你可以那样做，实际上你不是
limited to one input channel you can
限于一个输入通道即可
have several of those which brings out
有几个带出来的
stream but what we need to do is you
流，但我们需要做的是您
have to credit I the challenge we are
必须归功于我的挑战
going to talk to
打算和
alright difficult it's not difficult it
好难不难
goes like this you have to provide an
这样，您必须提供一个
interface how we are going to call those
接口我们将如何称呼那些
channels let's say car channels make
假设汽车频道让
sense a good name cool and you will have
感觉好名字很酷，您将拥有
in this case how many channels you set
在这种情况下，您设置了多少个频道
so we're going to listen for let's say
所以我们要听我们说
information about braking and the
有关制动的信息
temperature right so I'm gonna have two
温度合适，我要两个
two input channels I guess two input
两个输入通道，我猜两个输入
channels one of them would be called
渠道之一将被称为
temperature right gonna be input channel
正确的温度将成为输入通道
subscriber channel temperature right is
用户频道温度正确为
there any typo I guess it's fine
我有错别字
and the other one was what and breaking
而另一个是什么，打破
oh breaking so we have two we have the
哦，打破，所以我们有两个，我们有
channels defined right so we have to
渠道定义正确，所以我们必须
enable channels in this case to those
在这种情况下启用渠道
two input channels okay that's the
两个输入通道好，那就是
difference right instead of think I'm
区别权利而不是认为我
passing the controller okay alright so
通过控制器好吧，所以
what we need to do more I'm going to do
我们需要做的更多
copy paste I guess you are familiar this
复制粘贴我想你对此很熟悉
is my favorite technique shouldn't you
是我最喜欢的技术吗
go to stack overflow first this this was
首先去堆栈溢出，这是
easy so I'm just going to do a copy
容易，所以我要去复印
paste so stream listener from the first
从第一个粘贴so流监听器
channel which was called temperature
称为温度的通道
right okay how do you want to handle
好的，你要如何处理
this make sense then is now then my
这是有意义的，然后现在是我的
guess so
我猜也是
what is the other one let's say we have
另一个是什么，我们说
a dictionary Asian value acceleration
字典亚洲价值加速
yes should be float or integers like
是的应该是浮点数或整数
with money it's alright
用钱没关系
so in breaking of the acceleration
所以在加速中
so the acceleration is now on the
所以加速度现在在
acceleration curse type about who cares
关于谁在乎的加速诅咒类型
right so if I just run run it right now
对，所以如果我现在就运行，请立即运行
will it work or do you need to do
它会工作还是您需要做
something more we have to do some sort
还有一些我们必须做的事情
of a configuration to tell the binder
告诉活页夹的配置
how to behave yes because we have two
如何表现是的，因为我们有两个
input channels right one is for
输入通道对一个是
temperature the other one is for braking
温度另一个用于制动
so how are we doing keywords in this
那么我们如何在其中做关键字
case it has one destination forum 50
如果它有一个目的地论坛50
messages am Q dot topic and then thanks
消息是Q点主题，然后谢谢
to the binding routing key the messages
到绑定路由键的消息
are going to be routed accordingly okay
将被相应地路由好吗
does it make sense yes
有道理吗
so what we need to do remember for the
所以我们需要记住的是
previous example no all right you're a
前面的例子，没有，你是
fast learner margin and I'm binding
快速的学习者保证金，我具有约束力
routing key it's gonna be this this time
路由键，这将是这次
temperature right yes all right the copy
温度正确是可以复制
place it's gonna be quicker and the
放置它会更快，
other one is I guess breaking okay pied
另一个我想打破还可以
including key there is no type of this
包括钥匙，没有这个类型
this time it's important so so it wasn't
这次很重要，所以不是
important the last time yes I see if I
上一次很重要，是的，我看看是否
now run it and we do some push from
现在运行它，我们从
mosquito to temperature topic and then
蚊子到温度主题，然后
to breaking topic we should see
打破主题，我们应该看到
different bloggers all right let's do
好吧，不同的博客写手
that any questions while it's putting
任何问题，而它把
absolutely not
绝对不
everything is clear nice I saw late
一切都很好，我迟到了
today
今天
all right that was a bad one do you want
好吧，那是你想要的一个坏人
to explain this so what's the message
解释一下，这是什么意思
when it comes to say it's 30 degrees
说到30度
Celsius all right doesn't look like this
摄氏好吧看起来不是这样
one is going to be sent to temperature
一个将被发送到温度
right yeah make sense let's do it why
是的，有道理，为什么要这样做
not
不
the other one was breaking yes and
另一个打破了是，
what's the braking acceleration it'd be
制动加速度是多​​少
fast yeah
快耶
braking as you can see it's printed out
可以看到它已经打印出来了
so it was super easy to have
所以这很容易
multi-channel support in one spring
一Spring 多渠道支持
sprinkle stream application right so now
现在撒流应用程序
we can just treat the messages
我们可以对待消息
accordingly I guess in your production
因此我想你的作品
is gonna beat something different than
会击败不同于
system dot out in
系统点进
inside right I don't think so anyways
内在，我仍然不这么认为
let's go back to the slice because I
让我们回到切片，因为我
want to show you the bigger picture of
想给你看大图
things you know there is a bigger
你知道的东西更大
picture absolutely we're an Enterprise
想像一下，我们绝对是一家企业
Architect it's always a bigger picture
建筑师，这始终是一幅大图
don't have so we have those cars you
没有，所以我们有那些车
know still there the cops and they emit
知道警察还在，他们散发出来
metrics so we have a lot of different
指标，所以我们有很多不同
teams doing all sorts of different
团队做各种不同的事情
things in a company like is it like is
公司里的事情是这样的
it a very concrete example of what we're
这是我们的一个非常具体的例子
doing in the company yes so the things
在公司做的事情是这样
are for example anomaly detection so
例如异常检测
there is an application somewhere that
某个地方有一个应用程序
gathers metrics from different places
从不同的地方收集指标
processes them by a different algorithms
通过不同的算法处理它们
you know machine learning all the
你知道机器学习的所有
buzzers and it's spring book based I can
蜂鸣器，这是我可以的 spring book
see what we have for example driver
看看我们有什么驱动程序
score so there is some sort of estate we
得分，所以我们有某种遗产
gets metrics and retrieve the state we
获取指标并检索我们的状态
match it somehow and we give a and score
以某种方式匹配它，我们给a和得分
to the driver Diagnostics it everything
给驾驶员诊断一切
is correct with the car again different
是正确的，与汽车再次不同
sources of data then the trip as well
数据来源，然后旅行
maybe some points of it just depending
也许它的某些要点取决于
on your location etc right so we are
在您的位置等正确，所以我们
doing an analysis of different sorts of
做各种不同的分析
data and basing on that we were having
数据，并以此为基础
some conclusions right so we'll be
一些正确的结论，所以我们会
joining different stream of information
加入不同的信息流
from the car to get different
从车上变得与众不同
conclusions and then what's the results
结论，然后是什么结果
so because until now we're just getting
所以因为到目前为止，我们只是
the data right getting ever the messages
数据权得到消息
what we would like to do right now is to
我们现在想做的是
send a claim notification like send a
发送索赔通知，例如发送
message to the car to the see drivers
消息到车上看司机
app something like this we'd like to
应用我们想要的东西
notify someone someone about the CD
通知某人有关CD的信息
analysis do we have done in other words
换句话说，我们做了分析吗
you want to populate an output channel
您要填充输出通道
like maybe for analytics or just your
例如可能用于分析或仅用于您的
car back exact get to know something is
开车回来确切地了解某事是
it difficult to be done it's a push
很难做到这是一个推动
information from sprinkle stream yes
来自撒流的信息是
it's super easy we want to see that sure
超级容易，我们想确保
let's try so let's say we are going to
让我们尝试，让我们说我们要
build this super cool animal detection
建立这种超酷的动物检测
algorithm right let's just say that it's
对的算法，让我们只说它是
an anomaly detector all right that's
一个异常检测器可以了
good that's a good start so I think we
好，这是一个好的开始，所以我认为我们
are going to copy place something as you
将要复制你的东西
all know here so in this time you are
都知道这里，所以这次你
going to talk to how many
要跟多少人说话
channels so we are pulling for messages
渠道，所以我们正在寻找消息
and we're going to send out a message so
我们将发送一条消息，以便
we have an input and output channel it
我们有一个输入和输出通道
makes sense the input channel is for
输入通道用于
what not going to be for breaking I
什么不会破坏我
guess okay because animal detection
猜测还可以，因为动物检测
works like this we are taking a look at
这样的作品，我们来看看
the breaking and then what example so we
突破，然后是什么例子，所以我们
could do some you know sophisticated
可以做一些你知道复杂的事情
logic there but that starts you know you
逻辑在那里，但那开始你知道你
have to start with PUC so let's do an if
必须从PUC开始，所以让我们做一个
statement alright
好的陈述
and the output challenge gonna be what
输出挑战将是什么
you're doing we're going to talk to
你正在做，我们要和
what's the name of this channel
这个频道叫什么名字
anomalies right if there's an anomaly
如果有异常就对
let's send it out to anomalies okay and
让我们将其发送到异常状态，然后
this time it's not subscribable channel
这次不是可订阅的频道
it's a message Channel that's how Splunk
这是一个Splunk的消息通道
icing works message channel we're going
我们将要结冰的消息频道
to call it animal is right about be good
称其为动物是正确的
okay we have to enable binding to car
好，我们必须启用绑定到汽车
channels as we used to do in the
频道，就像我们以前在
previous examples enable binding our
前面的示例可以绑定我们的
channel's class right something more I
频道的课程对我来说更重要
mean they need the analogic right so you
表示他们需要类比权利，所以您
would have this complex logic going to
会有这种复杂的逻辑去
the database doing ai ai okay whatever
数据库在做ai ai好的
all the acronyms all right consumer
所有首字母缩写词好吧消费者
Jenny contracts maybe here CDC all right
珍妮可能在这里与CDC签约
something more no that's it CDC is good
更重要的是CDC很好
enough all right
够了吧
so but for this demo what is the actual
所以对于这个演示，实际的是什么
machine learning algorithm it's a very
机器学习算法，这是一个非常
stupid machine so if the acceleration is
愚蠢的机器，所以如果加速度是
greater than 30 for example it's then
例如大于30
what is something like send out the
发出什么像
message I guess right let's log it out
消息，我猜对了，让我们注销
maybe other source logging is important
也许其他源日志记录很重要
what right yes well and now since it's
是的，现在是正确的，因为它是
not the message you want to send the
不是您要发送的邮件
message to this channel someone do the
向此频道发送消息的人
way to inject this car channels into
注入汽车通道的方式
here I cry about final car channels i
在这里，我为最终的汽车频道而哭泣
reconstructed course okay and then you
重建课程好，然后你
are able to do this car challenge dot
能够做这辆车挑战点
anomalies send new message I said what
异常发送新消息我说什么
you want to sound like bored or what
你想听起来像无聊还是什么
what is good so if I do that we like
有什么好处，所以如果我愿意，我们喜欢
descriptive messages this is so this is
描述性消息是这样的
what the driver is going to see
驾驶员将会看到什么
that's good enough if you want that
如果你想要那已经足够了
that's for sure it sounds like an
可以肯定，这听起来像
anomaly so that's exactly what the
异常，这正是
driver should get all right let's do
司机应该没事吧
this kind of anomaly detection if I run
如果我运行这种异常检测
this application right now
此应用程序现在
what does I guess configuration
我猜怎么配置
yeah configuration makes sense you are a
是的配置很有意义，您是
fast learner man thank you so much
快速学习的人非常感谢你
so configurations here what we need to
所以在这里配置我们需要
pass so in the previous example we pass
通过，因此在前面的示例中，我们通过
by a putting key for the input channel
通过输入通道的推键
the same we have to do in here right
我们在这里要做的一样
so Vampira including key is breaking
所以包括钥匙在内的Vampira都坏了
right yeah you are streaming information
是的，您正在流式传输信息
from the events related to breaking
从与破坏有关的事件
patterns of your appear of your car and
您的车模外观和
we have to pass something to the
我们必须传递一些东西给
producer side to actually route the
生产方实际路由
message accordingly this is the first
消息因此这是第一个
time we're sending out a message right
正确的时间发送信息
yes it works like this root link key
是的，它像这个根链接键一样工作
expression it's gonna be anomalies or
表达它将是异常的
dot anomalies right right and thanks to
点异常正确对，并感谢
this setup each time you are going to
每次您要进行此设置时
talk to your output channel it's gonna
与您的输出频道交谈
be populated with this routing key
使用此路由密钥填充
expression and probably we can hear this
表达，也许我们可以听到
information somewhere oh yeah so um this
信息在某处哦，是的，所以这个
is interesting what just said because we
刚才说的很有趣，因为我们
have the CLI to send out a message so we
有CLI发送消息，所以我们
simulated a car uh-huh but now we would
模拟了一辆车，但是现在我们会
have to have some sort of a process that
必须有某种过程，
will fetch the message right right so
会正确地获取消息，因此
you are looking for an equivalent of
您正在寻找的等价物
mosquito published for subscription yeah
蚊子已经发布订阅了
so it's gotten mosquitos subscription
所以它得到了蚊子订阅
right it was a good name yeah
对，这是一个好名字
so let's say we are streaming
假设我们正在流式传输
information we are subscribing to a
我们正在订阅的信息
second channel which will be a topic
第二个频道将成为主题
which will be named anomalies solemnize
这将被命名为异常庄严
right and the local host is still there
正确，本地主机仍在
the port is default the username was
默认端口是用户名
user right and the passport was passed
用户权利和护照已通过
and the topics what are we passing our
和主题，我们通过了什么
production credentials here it's not
生产凭证不是
production is my local machine man we
生产是我的本地机器人，我们
have the same ones in production all
全部生产相同
right
对
I didn't know that now you do like
我不知道你现在喜欢
everybody what's there was a topic
每个人都有一个话题
anomalies anomalies right yeah so if I
是的，异常，是的，如果我
type enter right now what shall we do so
现在输入Enter我们应该怎么做
this is the process is waiting for a
这是过程正在等待
message to
讯息给
right subscribe ok so I guess we need to
正确订阅好，所以我想我们需要
send the message with a temperature
发送带有温度的消息
right OH
对哦
the breaking as a drink sorry so we need
喝点饮料对不起，所以我们需要
to create an animal in other words yeah
用另一种方式创造动物
what's the other money over 30 over 40
还有30多40多的钱
so I'm going to push something with 29
所以我要用29推动
of that should work or not and we
其中应该工作或不工作，我们
shouldn't get any messages right so all
应该不会收到任何正确的消息
right send a couple of those all right
正确发送一些正确的
now you take out the subscription here
现在您在这里取出订阅
it goes okay nothing there so now
现在那里什么也没事
theoretically if we didn't mess anything
从理论上讲，如果我们什么都没弄乱
up which is impossible during life
在生活中这是不可能的
coding it doesn't happen we should get a
编码不会发生，我们应该得到一个
message over there right send a couple
那里的消息发送一对
more like sure okay so that's an
更像是肯定的好，那是
explicit message alright good so let's
明确的消息好吧，让我们
take a look at the application logs as
看看应用程序日志为
you can see the animal is detected
你可以看到动物被检测到
clearly good right that's absolutely
显然是好的权利，这是绝对的
great so we managed so let's recap we've
太好了，我们设法做到了，让我们回顾一下
managed to use spring integration as an
设法使用spring集成作为
implementation of an enterprise
企业实施
integration pattern to pause the
集成模式以暂停
messages we could also most likely
我们也很可能会收到的消息
leverage it to send out messages right
利用它正确发送消息
yes we've managed to spirit off stream
是的，我们设法摆脱了困境
to stream data and write listeners and
流数据并编写侦听器，以及
senders of messages in a very fast way
邮件发件人的速度非常快
correct now we have those teams right
正确，现在我们有那些团队了
and let's say the anomaly detector uses
假设异常检测器使用
different sorts of data sources of data
不同种类的数据源
to do to do the analysis okay that does
做分析就可以了
assume now that a couple of new sources
现在假设有两个新来源
are required right so they we have to
是必需的，所以我们必须
write some code etc you know to redeploy
写一些您知道要重新部署的代码
it it can be done right but you know I'm
它可以做对但你知道我
an Enterprise Architect I need tools
我需要工具的企业架构师
that are free have a UI and a decent so
免费的用户界面和像样的
I would like DSL do enterprise
我想DSL做企业
architecting of course oh or graphs so
当然是架构师哦或图
what I would like to achieve is that the
我想实现的是
teams can leverage some sort of a DSL or
团队可以利用某种DSL或
graphs to pipe the data you know zip
图形来传送您知道的zip数据
them do whatever they need to filter out
他们做任何需要过滤的事情
and without actually writing a lot of
并没有实际写很多
code so you're saying that oh you're a
代码，所以您说的是，哦，您是
great consultant so you're gonna just
伟大的顾问，所以您将只是
rip they say again what I just said in
撕开他们再说我刚才说的话
your own words that's what we do and
你自己的话就是我们要做的
you're gonna be paid for that you're
你会因为你而得到报酬
saying you want those components to be
说您希望这些组件成为
usable and composable and create some
可用和可组合并创建一些
stream of informations
信息流
better denied it okay yeah that's what I
最好否认它，是的，那是我的意思
wanted to achieve yes have you heard
想实现是，你听说过吗
about spring cloud dataflow if I do
关于 Spring Cloud 数据流，如果我这样做
during about I wouldn't ask you about
在约期间，我不会问你
this I didn't you didn't okay so have
这个我不是，你不知道，所以有
you have you heard about Spring eggs
你听说过春鸡蛋
no B that I heard yes can you describe
不，我听到是B，你能形容
it so that was a application that allows
它是一个允许
you to you know spawn sings processors
您知道您会生成处理器
and sources like inside the same process
和相同流程中的资源
right so it wasn't really cloud native
对，所以它不是真正的云原生
right what was the problem of that may
对，那可能是什么问题
be scaling yes it was a collimator
可以缩放，是准直仪
because it was inside the processor is
因为它在处理器内部
difficult to scale so it had its own
很难扩展，所以它有自己的
problems well it rewritten to like
问题很好，它改写为喜欢
something cloud native yes you can use
云原生是的，您可以使用
actual sprinkled dataflow which solves
实际的分散数据流解决了
this problem like it's actually you can
像这样的问题，实际上你可以
scale those applications compose them
扩展那些应用程序
the composed of sinks sources processors
由接收器源处理器组成
that are created by your balance themes
由您的余额主题创建的
and proof to some repository right so
并证明一些存储库是正确的
you're saying that what right now those
你是说现在那些
things sources and processor are
事物来源和处理器是
separate spring good applications yes
单独的Spring 良好的应用是
okay and you can reuse them to compose
好的，您可以重复使用它们来撰写
and govern streams of information okay
并管理信息流还可以
so how do you package your application
那么如何打包您的应用程序
by the way applications to be some of
顺便说一下应用程序
them are sent by emails some of them are
它们是通过电子邮件发送的，其中一些是
jars all right what else that's it
罐子没事，那是什么
that's it okay so I'm sad to report that
就这样好了，所以我很伤心地报告，
sprinkled data flow doesn't support
分散的数据流不支持
emailing but it supports jars and docker
通过电子邮件发送，但它支持jar和docker
images and maven coordinate so we can
图像和行家坐标，所以我们可以
actually point to different repositories
实际上指向不同的存储库
for applications for spring with
用于Spring
applications right okay and then what it
应用程序正常，然后呢
does is going to create a stream of
确实会创建一个
information connecting all of the things
连接所有事物的信息
sources and processors using sprinkle
源和处理器使用洒
stream so the abstraction you have seen
流，所以您已经看到了抽象
like 20 minutes ago so you're saying
例如20分钟前
that it's actually you're able to
实际上，您能够
describe a flow of data that's why it's
描述数据流的原因
called data flow yes it's even driven
叫做数据流，是的，甚至被驱动
streaming right using sprinkle stream
使用洒水流直接流
but there are also like short-lived
但也有短暂的
applications like let's say like every
像每个应用程序一样
now and then you want to do some
时不时你想做一些
batching right send some information to
批处理权发送一些信息到
to your car that there's some detection
在您的车上有一些检测
of Diagnostics coming or something this
诊断即将到来
right right so we can then use sprinkle
对对，所以我们可以用洒
task to do so awesome where do you
如此出色的任务，您在哪里
actually deploy your applications what
实际部署您的应用程序
do you use laptops
你用笔记本电脑吗
[Music]
[音乐]
which one we have actually both left
我们实际上都离开了哪一个
communities in cloth hungry great so
布饿的社区很棒
actually when you create those flows
实际上当您创建这些流程时
right these are not deployed yet and
对，这些还没有部署
then sprinkled flow it's agnostic to the
然后洒水对它是不可知的
target runtime so we can actually deploy
目标运行时，因此我们可以实际部署
it to my local machine which we are
它到我们本地的机器上
going to do soon or you can just deploy
快去做，或者您可以部署
to communities or country okay doesn't
去社区或国家好吗
make sense great
很有道理
so to recap does that that's how the
回顾一下，这就是
architecture of sprinkle dataflow may
分散数据流的架构可能
look like so we have a dataflow server
看起来像这样，我们有一个数据流服务器
which is responsible for recognizing
负责识别
what the stream what is the stream that
什么流是什么流
we were passing by a DSL or maybe Yui or
我们通过DSL或Yui或
might be found via some sort of a shop
可能通过某种商店找到
okay and it has its keeper server have
好吧，它有它的守护者服务器
you heard about skipper server no so
您没有听说过船长服务器
second a system that performs rolling
第二个执行滚动的系统
upgrades and deployment of your
您的升级和部署
applications that are part of your
属于您的应用程序
streams okay is it free it's free
流免费，它是免费的
okay it has a new way as well let's do
好吧，它也有新的方法
it right so then what skipper does is
没错，那么船长要做的是
going to deploy out the implement all of
将部署所有的工具
the applications and govern the whole
应用程序和整体治理
stream on your target runtime like local
在您的目标运行时流，例如本地
machine kubernetes yes right okay so
机器kubernetes是的，好的，所以
just by accident sprinkled dataflow
只是偶然散布的数据流
server and skipper is running on my
服务器和队长正在我的
machine right now what is the price so
机器现在价格是多少
they want to see de DUI course I want to
他们想看我想去的DUI课程
see it is why is the most important
看到这就是为什么最重要
shape is somewhere in here is it nice
形状在这里某处很好
you know you're going to tell me this is
你知道你要告诉我这是
how it looks like it's nice it's nice we
看起来很好，很好，我们
can use it you can use it right so you
可以使用它，你可以正确使用它，所以你
have to actually teach dataflow that
必须实际教导数据流
there are certain apps that you're
您有某些应用
balanced improved somewhere right okay I
平衡改善了，好吧，我
just maven or maybe those docker image
只是行家或那些码头工人形象
which I can compose the flow yeah okay
我可以组成流程了，好吧
so we can go in here and actually I did
所以我们可以进入这里，实际上我做了
that before all okay our representation
在我们一切就绪之前
because I knew you would ask about that
因为我知道你会问这个
so these are the apps that you can
这些是您可以使用的应用
actually push as you can see some of
正如您所看到的，
them from my local machine this one file
他们从我的本地计算机这一个文件
this is this anomaly detector yeah it's
这是这个异常检测器，是的
there are some also done by spring but
Spring 也做了一些，但是
by spring team a couple of processors
Spring 团队的几个处理器
sayings from files from FTP from Delphi
来自Delphi的FTP文件中的谚语
etc etc okay so we can do whatever you
等等等等，好吧，我们可以做任何你想做的
want in here right and actually how to
想在这里，实际上如何
prove those applications you can just
证明您可以使用的那些应用程序
add an application here we can do bulk
在这里添加应用程序，我们可以批量
import you can
可以导入
mr. one that when it comes to that's it
先生。一说到就可以了
when it comes to you I you can do the
当涉及到你我可以
same or less the same by our show in
在我们的节目中相同或不相同
here like we can invest even up another
就像我们可以在这里投资一样
my detector we passed and what the
我通过的探测器以及
application is what the type of the
应用程序是什么类型的
application is it thing is it source
应用程序是它的源头
maybe it's a processor maybe it's a
也许是处理器，也许是
shortwave task okay so this code works
短波任务好吧，所以这段代码有效
right and so once they are registered
对，因此一旦注册
you are almost ready to create a stream
您几乎准备创建流
what have seemed you want to create
您似乎想要创建什么
let's say that the message comes in from
假设邮件来自
HTTP like somebody sends a post all
像有人一样HTTP都发帖
right HTTP oh yeah there is this nice
正确的HTTP哦，是的，这很不错
can you drag and drop the next one
您可以拖放下一个吗
what's the next one we would put for
我们接下来要买的是什么
example is anomaly detector animal
例子是异常检测器动物
detector okay so we can actually do this
检测器好吧，所以我们实际上可以做到这一点
and this I can compose that right okay
这样我就可以写好了
that's cool but actually the anomaly
那很酷，但实际上是异常现象
detector is actually filter yeah so we
检测器实际上是过滤器，是的，所以我们
can use a filter you can use the
可以使用过滤器，也可以使用
component from spring gripper and what's
Spring 夹爪的组件以及什么
called filter why not okay
叫过滤器为什么不行
I'm going to change out so actually you
我要换衣服，所以实际上你
can just drag-and-drop you can pass it
只需拖放即可通过
wire DSL you can use the show that you
可以用DSL线显示你
have seen as well great so the thing of
看起来很棒，所以
the information
信息
system.out.println I'll okay all right
system.out.println我会好的
so I'm going to pass the log okay make
所以我要通过日志，好使
sense yes so this is how to create the
是的，所以这是如何创建
stream it's not deployed yet what's the
流尚未部署，这是什么
name of the stream anomaly detector I
流异常检测器的名称I
guess yeah
猜对
detector good create the stream it's
检测器好创建它的流
created but it's not deployed as you can
已创建，但尚未部署
see it says it's on deployed alright so
看到它说它已经部署好了，所以
now what we have to do is we have to
现在我们要做的是
deploy it to my local machine what don't
将其部署到我的本地计算机上
we have to configure it in some way yes
我们必须以某种方式配置它
if you click this is going to ask you to
如果您单击，这将要求您
pass on some sort of properties for
传递某种属性
instance via you have three applications
实例通过您有三个应用程序
right source processor and sync let's
正确的源处理器并同步
configure the source what is it what's
配置源是什么
the number of the port I know six five
我知道的港口数量六五
four three
四三
this is better I guess oh because you
我猜这更好，因为你
have all the scripts papers for you to
有所有脚本文件供您选择
sign
标志
exactly how about filtering how do you
究竟如何过滤您如何
want to filter out like what's the
想要像什么一样过滤掉
alimony now I'm afraid to ask even you
养费现在我也不敢问你
know because if you get everything try
知道，因为如果一切都尝试
to go
去
I'll pass like this okay that's what I
这样我就可以过去了
wanted to suggest payload different than
想建议不同于
30 that's another one of course all
30那当然是全部
right let's do that so we you can
正确，让我们这样做，这样我们就可以
configure those applications there are
配置那些应用程序有
still not deployed if I click deploy
如果单击“部署”仍未部署
right now to deploy them to your local
现在将它们部署到您的本地
machine yes and now we can go to the
机器是的，现在我们可以去
runtime and see that there are free
运行时，看到有空闲
applications almost deployed on my local
应用程序几乎部署在我的本地
machine so three separate screen with
机所以三个独立的屏幕
applications running right all of them
正确运行所有应用程序
they create a stream of information
他们创建信息流
that's that's responsible for animal
那就是动物的责任
detection so are you saying that you
检测，所以你是说你
don't even have to create a controller
甚至不必创建控制器
in it of anything because for example
在任何事情上，例如
with the HTTP up he's gonna have already
有了HTTP，他就已经拥有了
the control yes that's awesome it works
控制是的，它很棒
out of the box so they are deployed
开箱即用，因此可以进行部署
right okay so if I do post to HTTP 80 82
好吧，如果我发布到HTTP 80 82
right now the number of 30 or 31 we
现在30或31
should see or we shouldn't see something
应该看到或我们不应该看到的东西
in the logs of the single if you sent 30
如果您发送了30，则在单曲的日志中
we're not going to see anything all
我们不会看到所有的东西
right if we're going to send anything
对，如果我们要发送任何东西
else we're gonna see something
否则我们会看到一些东西
I hope it's prepared yes so if we do HD
我希望它是准备的，所以如果我们做高清
post to my local host 8080 to 29 right
发布到我的本地主机8080到29
where is the that's let's do the second
那是第二个
one as well
一个也
31 okay right and 40 so we assume that
31好的，40，所以我们假设
we're gonna see two entries in the logs
我们将在日志中看到两个条目
yeah and that's my understanding
是的，那是我的理解
so let's check where the locks or if you
因此，让我们检查一下锁的位置，或者
just go in here to the sync application
只需在这里进入同步应用程序
you can see that there is done an output
您可以看到已经完成了输出
in here right okay so if I go there
在这里好吧，如果我去那里
right now
马上
but here but I may be here tail you see
但在这里但我可能在这里
- a - log statements right that's great
-一个-正确的日志语句
so that's one of my detection works like
所以这是我的检测工作之一
a charm
魅力
so it even works much to my surprise
所以它甚至使我惊讶
yeah so it comes with an audit log as
是的，所以它附带了一个审核日志
well you can do we can create short if
好吧，我们可以做空
task there's a rolling upgrades
任务有滚动升级
possibilities it says that's wrong so
它说错的可能性，所以
it's like a really rich tool I was okay
就像一个很好的工具，我还可以
that's that's awesome so the last
那很棒，所以最后
question is because it's running on your
问题是因为它正在您的计算机上运行
laptop is there an option to actually
笔记本电脑实际上有一个选项
have it running in the cloud yes so I
让它在云中运行是的，所以我
have my PW Apps account you can have
拥有我的PW Apps帐户
yours as well of services
您的服务
yes so the internet connection is kind
是的，所以互联网连接很好
of slow let's see if I can get it logged
慢点让我们看看是否可以记录下来
in any questions no oh yeah so I have my
任何问题都没有哦是的，所以我有我的
domain in here and I have a couple of
域在这里，我有几个
services so if you go to marketplace
服务，所以如果你去市场
it's for free by the way I mean until
我的意思是免费的，直到
some point of course you can go to
当然可以去
marketplace and see that this there is
市场，看到这里
data full server so ok this is what we
数据已满的服务器，好的，这就是我们
are looking for right there is data
正在寻找正确的数据
source data store for spinkle data flow
尖峰数据流的源数据存储
because it makes sense right
因为这很有意义
and there is the messaging
还有消息
infrastructure to connect those
连接那些的基础设施
applications awesome like grab your
很棒的应用程序，例如抓住您的
Kafka okay right so I picked all of them
卡夫卡好吧，所以我都选了
previously as my services you can see
以前作为我的服务您可以看到
right DB messaging and the data flow
正确的数据库消息传递和数据流
itself right ok so if I click in here I
本身就可以，所以如果我在这里单击
can actually manage my applications in
可以实际管理我的应用程序
the cloud and I can do as we have seen
云，我们可以做到
on my local machine I can push
在我的本地机器上，我可以推动
coordinates to my applications and then
协调到我的应用程序，然后
I can create streams etc etc I can
我可以创建流等，我可以
govern them I can deploy I can upgrade I
管理他们，我可以部署，我可以升级，
can check the outlet locks ok so maybe
可以检查出口锁好，所以也许
one day it's going to start it started
有一天要开始了
so so it's exactly the same thing you
所以这跟你完全一样
had running on your local machine but
在您的本地计算机上运行，​​但是
you have it in the cloud so as a user
您将其存储在云中，以便作为用户
experience nothing really changes
没有经历什么真正的改变
nothing will change except for the fact
除了事实之外，什么都不会改变
that this time data flow or to be more
这次数据流或更多
precise skipper server is going to
精确的船长服务器将
perform deployment to my cloud account
执行部署到我的云帐户
right up to my local machine
就在我的本地机器上
so I can actually prove the same
所以我可以证明相同
application then anomaly detector there
应用程序，然后在那里异常检测器
ok right any more questions about this I
好的，关于这个我还有其他问题吗
have no more questions you have no more
没有更多的问题，没有更多的问题
questions do you want to see like maybe
您是否想看到类似的问题
stream show it to me so it's in the
流向我展示，所以它在
cloud what do you want to do like the
云你想做什么像
same thing yeah you can do like
是的，你可以喜欢
time-based something and then log it out
基于时间的东西，然后注销
right but that's a very good stream wait
是的，但这是一个非常好的流等待
stream absolutely you want to filter
流绝对要过滤
that like this if I click create stream
如果我单击创建流，就这样
the same happens right as we used to do
就像我们过去一样发生
and if I deploy is going to deploy to my
如果我要部署到我的
PCF account right I need to pass some
PCF帐户权​​利，我需要通过一些
filtering logic and the pass maybe in
过滤逻辑和通过可能
Toronto Newark is enough in this case
在这种情况下，多伦多纽瓦克就足够了
it's going to be paid
它会被支付
different than 40 right okay let's try
不同于40吧，让我们尝试
it
它
deploy the stream yeah
部署流是的
and it's going to deploy free spring
它将部署自由 Spring
with applications to my PCF account
申请到我的PCF帐户
right what have you learned so far I
对，到目前为止你学到了什么
learned that we tell you too much that's
得知我们告诉你太多了
for sure
当然
I managed to learn that spring
我设法在那个 Spring 学习
integration is an implementation of
整合是
enterprise integration patterns and it
企业集成模式及其
allows us to use like to connect to the
允许我们使用like连接到
MQTT broker it's one of the adapters of
MQTT经纪人，它的适配器之一
those I've learned that sprinkle stream
我学到的那些洒水
is a nice abstraction we can say spring
可以说是 Spring 的美好抽象
integration on steroids to pull and push
整合类固醇以推动和推动
messages to the broker I managed to
给经纪人的邮件
learn that wait wait wait
学习，等待，等待，等待
it is broker agnostic oh yeah it's very
这是经纪人不可知的哦，是的，非常
agnostic and how does it work so
不可知论，以及它如何运作
depending on what you have in a class
取决于你在课堂上有什么
buff it it's it can connect to different
buff它可以连接到其他
brokers right all right also if I'm I
如果我是经纪人，也可以
can guess if you have multiple brokers
可以猜测您是否有多个经纪人
on the class path you can configure
在您可以配置的类路径上
which channel would use which which
哪个渠道会使用哪个渠道
broke that's funky and sprinkles film
打破了时髦，并洒了电影
uses what underneath it's rectification
使用其正下方的内容
correct and I've learned that we can use
正确，我了解到我们可以使用
sprinkle dataflow to govern let's say
撒数据流来控制，比如说
streams of flows of data and what of
数据流以及什么
what are the two most important kinds of
最重要的两种是什么
those clothes so we have like two three
那些衣服，所以我们有两个三
I guess syncs sources and processors
我想同步源和处理器
right but there are like shortly if
是的，但是如果
annoy yeah we have the short-lived and
是的，我们很短暂
like sprinkle tasks will be executed
像是洒任务
underneath for the short-lived tasks and
在短期任务下面
we have the Monson we can deploy to
我们有可以部署到的Monson
let's say various locations like a local
比方说本地
machine or a platform like Cobras or and
机器或平台，例如眼镜蛇或
it supports different packaging when it
它支持不同的包装
comes to up the caps what kind to jars
盖上什么样的罐子
may be leaving coordinates files or
可能正在离开坐标文件或
docker images I guess right do I have to
我猜是正确的docker镜像
add that it doesn't matter if you use
补充一点，如果您使用
Kafka or rabbit in queue to connect
卡夫卡或兔子排队等候
those same sources and processors since
这些相同的来源和处理器，因为
you have just said it I don't think yes
你刚刚说了我不认为是
correct
正确
thank you and then what have you learned
谢谢，然后你学到了什么
at the very end but you can use a spring
在最后但您可以使用Spring
data flow where I said it you can use it
我说过可以使用的数据流
in the cloud for you know I wasn't
在云中，因为你知道我不是
missing yet
失踪了
so they have any more questions I don't
所以他们还有其他问题，我没有
I will send you my invoice like why I
我会寄给我我的发票给我
email as the don't call us we'll call
用电子邮件发送，不要打给我们，我们打给
you
您
so do you have any questions then any
所以你有什么问题吗
questions who thinks it makes any sense
质疑谁认为这有意义
okay five people six six one who doesn't
好五个人六六一谁不
care at all like zero okay there are two
完全喜欢零，好吗，有两个
people good any questions so if you
人们会问任何问题，所以如果你
would like to see the code like if
想看的代码，如果
you're interested it's there all the
你有兴趣吗
demos that we have done today it's it's
我们今天完成的演示是
there so have any questions you can find
那里有什么问题可以找到
us on Twitter
我们在推特上
Jakub P dominant in my stack
雅各布P在我的游戏中占主导地位
and if you shy and I want to ask the
如果你害羞，我想问
question right now you can come to us
现在问你可以来找我们
and ask me questions just a second so
再问我一秒钟
thank you very much
非常感谢你
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]